(this.webpackJsonpquiz=this.webpackJsonpquiz||[]).push([[0],{51:function(e,t,a){e.exports=a(80)},79:function(e,t,a){},80:function(e,t,a){"use strict";a.r(t);var n=a(1),r=a.n(n),s=a(20),o=a.n(s),i=a(7),l=a(8),c=a(13),u=a(10),h=a(9),d=a(46),p=a(93),m=a(81),f=a(82),g=a(83),y=a(47),w=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(i.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).handleRuleClick=n.handleRuleClick.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.state={isRuleShow:!1},n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"handleRuleClick",value:function(){this.setState({isRuleShow:!this.state.isRuleShow})}},{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement("button",{className:"specialbuttons",onClick:this.handleRuleClick},"Rule Reference"),r.a.createElement(p.a,{className:"modal-xl",isOpen:this.state.isRuleShow},r.a.createElement(m.a,null,"Rule:",this.props.rulenum),r.a.createElement(f.a,null,r.a.createElement("iframe",{src:this.props.hrf,title:"Rulebook Documentation for Rule:".concat(this.props.rulenum," (Test ID: ").concat(this.props.name,")")})),r.a.createElement(g.a,null,r.a.createElement(y.a,{onClick:this.handleRuleClick},"Cancel"))))}}]),a}(r.a.Component),k=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(){return Object(i.a)(this,a),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.props.onegraded,t=this.props.showanswer,a=this.props.data2.correctanswer,n="https://www.usahockeyrulebook.com/page/show/"+this.props.rulelink+"/#panelTwo";if(!0===e){if(!0===t)return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionfooter"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"wrong"},"Incorrect"),r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(w,{grade:this.props.onegraded,hrf:n,rulenum:this.props.rulenum,name:this.props.name})),r.a.createElement("div",null,"Correct Answer: ",a));if(!0!==t){if(!0===this.props.correct)return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionfooter"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"right"},"Correct"),r.a.createElement(w,{grade:this.props.onegraded,hrf:n,rulenum:this.props.rulenum,name:this.props.name}));if(!0!==this.props.correct)return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionfooter"},r.a.createElement("p",{className:"wrong"}," Incorrect "),r.a.createElement(w,{grade:this.props.onegraded,hrf:n,rulenum:this.props.rulenum,name:this.props.name}),r.a.createElement("button",{className:"specialbuttons",onClick:this.props.showanswerclick},"Correct Answer"))}}if(!0!==e)return r.a.createElement("div",null)}}]),a}(r.a.Component),b=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(i.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).handleShowOneAnsClick=n.handleShowOneAnsClick.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.state={isOneGraded:n.props.graded,isShowOneAnswer:!1,answerorder:[],isCorrect:!1},n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"componentDidUpdate",value:function(e){this.props.graded!==e.graded&&(this.setState({isOneGraded:this.props.graded,isShowOneAnswer:!1}),!1===this.props.graded&&this.setState({answerorder:[],isCorrect:!1}),!1!==this.props.graded&&!0===this.state.isCorrect&&this.props.addpoints())}},{key:"handleAnswerClick",value:function(e,t){var a=e===this.props.data1.correctanswer;this.setState({isCorrect:a})}},{key:"handleShowOneAnsClick",value:function(){this.setState({isShowOneAnswer:!0})}},{key:"render",value:function(){for(var e=this,t=[],a=this.props.answers,n=this.props.name,s=function(){var s=void 0,i=e.state.answerorder;if(!1===e.props.graded){var l=a[e.props.shuffleanswers[o]];i=i.push(l),s=e.state.answerorder[o]}!1!==e.props.graded&&(s=i[o]),t.push(r.a.createElement("div",{key:n+o},r.a.createElement("ul",null,r.a.createElement("label",null,r.a.createElement("li",{className:"answers"},r.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",disabled:e.state.isOneGraded,name:n,id:s,onClick:function(){return e.handleAnswerClick(s,e.state.isOneGraded)}}),s)))))},o=0;o<a.length;o++)s();return r.a.createElement("div",null,t,r.a.createElement(k,{showanswerclick:this.handleShowOneAnsClick,showanswer:this.state.isShowOneAnswer,onegraded:this.state.isOneGraded,name:n,data2:this.props.data1,rulelink:this.props.data1.rulelink,rulenum:this.props.data1.rulenum,correct:this.state.isCorrect}))}}]),a}(r.a.Component),v=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(){return Object(i.a)(this,a),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("p",{className:"question-count questions"},this.props.num+1)}}]),a}(r.a.Component),A=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(){return Object(i.a)(this,a),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(v,{data2:this.props.data2,id1:this.props.id,num:this.props.num}),r.a.createElement("p",{className:"question-asked questions",tabIndex:"0"},this.props.data2[this.props.id].question))}}]),a}(r.a.Component),T=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(){return Object(i.a)(this,a),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.props.graded;return!0===e?r.a.createElement("button",{className:"grade",onClick:this.props.resetallclick},"Reset Test"):!0!==e?r.a.createElement("button",{className:"grade",onClick:this.props.gradeallclick},"Grade Test"):void 0}}]),a}(r.a.Component),q=a(50),O=function(e,t){for(var a=Object(q.a)(e),n=[];a.length>0;){var r=Math.floor(Math.random()*a.length);n.push(a[r]),a.splice(r,1)}return n},C=function(e){var t=("0"+Math.floor(e/3600)).slice(-2),a=("0"+Math.floor((e-3600*t)/60)).slice(-2),n=("0"+(e-(3600*t+60*a))).slice(-2);return t<1?a+":"+n:t+":"+a+":"+n};"04".slice(-2);var E=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(i.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).handleGradeAllClick=n.handleGradeAllClick.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.handleResetAllClick=n.handleResetAllClick.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.handleCorrectAnswer=n.handleCorrectAnswer.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.state={isAllGraded:!1,questionorder:[],numcorrect:0,time:0},n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"startTimer",value:function(){this.setState((function(e){return{time:e.time+=1}}))}},{key:"componentDidMount",value:function(){var e=this;this.timer=setInterval((function(){return e.startTimer()}),1e3)}},{key:"handleGradeAllClick",value:function(){window.location.href="#header".concat(this.props.id),clearInterval(this.timer),this.setState({isAllGraded:!0})}},{key:"handleCorrectAnswer",value:function(){this.setState((function(e){return{numcorrect:e.numcorrect+1}}))}},{key:"handleResetAllClick",value:function(){var e=this;window.location.href="#header".concat(this.props.id),this.timer=setInterval((function(){return e.startTimer()}),1e3),this.setState({isAllGraded:!1,questionorder:[],numcorrect:0,time:0});var t,a=Object(d.a)(document.querySelectorAll("input[name$=test".concat(this.props.id,"]")));try{for(a.s();!(t=a.n()).done;){t.value.checked=!1}}catch(n){a.e(n)}finally{a.f()}}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=[],t=this.props.data,a=this.state.numcorrect,n=t.length,s=C(this.state.time),o=0;n>0&&(o=Math.round(a/n*100)),e.push(r.a.createElement("h5",{className:"testheader",key:this.props.id+"timerresponse"},"Timer: ",s)),e.push(r.a.createElement("h5",{className:"testheader",key:this.props.id},"Score: ",a,"/",n," = ",o,"%"));for(var i=Array.from(Array(this.props.data.length).keys()),l=O(i),c=0;c<t.length;c++){var u=void 0,h=this.state.questionorder;if(!1===this.state.isAllGraded){var d=l[c];h=h.push(d),u=this.state.questionorder[c]}!1!==this.state.isAllGraded&&(u=h[c]);var p=t[u].incorrectanswers?t[u].incorrectanswers.concat(t[u].correctanswer):[],m=Array.from(Array(p.length).keys()),f=O(m);e.push(r.a.createElement(A,{data2:t,id:u,key:u,num:c})),e.push(r.a.createElement(b,{graded:this.state.isAllGraded,data1:t[u],answers:p,shuffleanswers:f,addpoints:this.handleCorrectAnswer,name:"question"+c.toString()+"test"+this.props.id,key:"question"+c.toString()+"test"+this.props.id}))}return r.a.createElement("div",null,e,r.a.createElement(T,{graded:this.state.isAllGraded,gradeallclick:this.handleGradeAllClick,resetallclick:this.handleResetAllClick,gradescore:this.handleIsCorrect}))}}]),a}(r.a.Component),S=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(){return Object(i.a)(this,a),t.apply(this,arguments)}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){for(var e=this.props.datafilter,t=[],a=0;a<e.length;a++){var n=Object.values(e[a].qa);t.push(r.a.createElement("div",{key:e[a].id},r.a.createElement("h4",{className:"testheader",id:"header".concat(e[a].id)}," ",e[a].book," - Level ",e[a].level," "),r.a.createElement(E,{id:e[a].id,data:n})))}return r.a.createElement("div",{className:"quiz-header"},t)}}]),a}(r.a.Component),j=a(84),F=a(85),N=a(86),P=a(87),I=a(88),z=a(89),R=a(94),H=a(95),U=a(90),M=a(91),G=a(92),x=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(i.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).togglec=n.togglec.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.toggleddUSAH=n.toggleddUSAH.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.toggleddHC=n.toggleddHC.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.toggleddNCAA=n.toggleddNCAA.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.state={isOpen:!1,dropdownUSAHOpen:!1,dropdownHCOpen:!1,dropdownNCAAOpen:!1},n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"togglec",value:function(){this.setState({isOpen:!this.state.isOpen})}},{key:"toggleddUSAH",value:function(){this.setState({dropdownUSAHOpen:!this.state.dropdownUSAHOpen})}},{key:"toggleddHC",value:function(){this.setState({dropdownHCOpen:!this.state.dropdownHCOpen})}},{key:"toggleddNCAA",value:function(){this.setState({dropdownNCAAOpen:!this.state.dropdownNCAAOpen})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this;return r.a.createElement("header",null,r.a.createElement(j.a,{color:"light",light:!0,expand:"md"},r.a.createElement(F.a,{href:"/"},"Ref Quiz"),r.a.createElement(N.a,{onClick:this.togglec}),r.a.createElement(P.a,{isOpen:this.state.isOpen,navbar:!0},r.a.createElement(I.a,{className:"mr-auto",navbar:!0},r.a.createElement(z.a,{nav:!0,isOpen:this.state.dropdownUSAHOpen,toggle:this.toggleddUSAH},r.a.createElement(R.a,{nav:!0,caret:!0},"USA Hockey"),r.a.createElement(H.a,null,r.a.createElement(U.a,{onClick:function(){return e.props.fclick("USA Hockey","1")}},"Level 1"),r.a.createElement(U.a,{onClick:function(){return e.props.fclick("USA Hockey","2")}},"Level 2"),r.a.createElement(U.a,{divider:!0}),r.a.createElement(U.a,null," ",r.a.createElement("a",{className:"dropdown-item",href:"https://www.usahockeyrulebook.com/page/show/1018524-appendix-i-summary-of-penalties/#panelTwo",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"}," Penalty Options")),r.a.createElement(U.a,null," ",r.a.createElement("a",{className:"dropdown-item",href:"https://www.usahockeyrulebook.com/page/show/1018525-appendix-ii-summary-of-face-off-locations/#panelTwo",target:"_blank",rel:"noopener noreferrer"},"Faceoff Locations")))),r.a.createElement(z.a,{nav:!0,isOpen:this.state.dropdownHCOpen,toggle:this.toggleddHC},r.a.createElement(R.a,{nav:!0,caret:!0},"Hockey Canada"),r.a.createElement(H.a,null,r.a.createElement(U.a,null,"Coming Soon"))),r.a.createElement(z.a,{nav:!0,isOpen:this.state.dropdownNCAAOpen,toggle:this.toggleddNCAA},r.a.createElement(R.a,{nav:!0,caret:!0},"NCAA"),r.a.createElement(H.a,null,r.a.createElement(U.a,null,"Coming Soon")))),r.a.createElement(I.a,{className:"ml-auto",navbar:!0},r.a.createElement(M.a,null,r.a.createElement(G.a,{target:"_blank",href:"https://hngodwin.com"},"Portfolio"))))))}}]),a}(r.a.Component),L=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(i.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).state={value:""},n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"render",value:function(){return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(p.a,{className:"modal-sm",isOpen:this.props.show},r.a.createElement(m.a,null,"Please Log In"),r.a.createElement("form",{onSubmit:this.props.showclick},r.a.createElement(f.a,null,r.a.createElement("label",{htmlFor:"username"},"Username:"),r.a.createElement("input",{type:"text",id:"username",name:"username",required:!0,onChange:this.props.user,value:this.props.value})),r.a.createElement(g.a,null,r.a.createElement("input",{type:"submit",name:"update_user",value:"Login"}),r.a.createElement("input",{type:"submit",name:"createnew_user",value:"Create Account"})))))}}]),a}(r.a.Component),B=[{id:"1usahall",book:"USA Hockey",level:"1",qa:[{id:"1usa1",rulelink:"1084672-rule-621-high-sticks",rulenum:"621d",question:"The determining point at which a shot is determined to be a 'slap shot' in a Girls 10U league is when the back swing goes higher than the waist.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa2",rulelink:"1062658-standard-of-play-casebook",rulenum:"Situation 5",question:"Under the standard of play initiative, a defensive player in front of the net may use their strength and balance to gain an advantageous body position on the opponent. This is permitted so long as they do not use their arms or stick to create space between them and the opponent or use their stick to impede the opponent's ability to move in a desired direction.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa3",rulelink:"1084676-rule-625-interference",rulenum:"625a(9)",question:"Any player on the players' or penalty bench who interferes, in any manner, with the movement of the puck on the ice while play is in progress, shall be assessed a minor penalty for_________?",correctanswer:"Interference",incorrectanswers:["Unsportsmanlike Conduct","Holding"]},{id:"1usa4",rulelink:"1084713-rule-634-slashing",rulenum:"634d",question:"An attacking player makes stick contact with the goalkeeper who has covered the puck and is in his/her crease. The whistle had not been blown yet. The proper action is:",correctanswer:"Assess the offending player a two minute minor penalty for slashing",incorrectanswers:["Warn the player that he/she should not to do that again","Give the goalkeeper a penalty for delay of game"]},{id:"1usa5",rulelink:"1084660-rule-613-face-off-procedures",rulenum:"613c",question:"After both teams have properly lined up for the face-off, the official conducting the face-off shall blow his/ her whistle to signal to both teams that he/she is about to drop the puck.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"1usa6",rulelink:"1084675-rule-624-icing-the-puck",rulenum:"624c",question:"Please indicate the proper face-off location: Icing error by officials",correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off spot",incorrectanswers:["Neutral Zone Face-off spot","Center Ice Face-off spot"]},{id:"1usa7",rulelink:"1084662-rule-614-falling-on-puck",rulenum:"614b",question:"With one minute left in the game, Team A removes their goaltender. A defender from Team A then covers the puck in their goal crease in an attempt to prevent a goal. The official can award a goal",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa8",rulelink:"1084477-rule-401-penalties",rulenum:"401b",question:"During the course of a youth hockey game Team A receives 15 penalties. The coach responsible for the team at the time of the 15th penalty is immediately given a _______.",correctanswer:"Game suspension and is ejected for the remainder of that game",incorrectanswers:["Bench minor and may stay on the bench for the remainder of that game","Game misconduct and is ejected for the remainder of that game and the following game"]},{id:"1usa9",rulelink:"1062658-standard-of-play-casebook",rulenum:"Situation 5",question:"According to the Standard of Play and Rules Emphasis, two players are battling in front of the goal and competing for body position. The defensive player uses the stick, with no extension of the arms, to 'steer' the attacking player in a desired direction. May this be considered cross-checking?",correctanswer:"No, there is nothing illegal about this action",incorrectanswers:["Yes, since the stick is exposed between the hands it must be enforced","Yes, steering is the same as impeding so it must be a penalty"]},{id:"1usa10",rulelink:"1084478-rule-402-minor-penalties",rulenum:"402b",question:"All bench minor penalties must be served by a non-penalized player who was on the ice at the time of the infraction, except the goalkeeper.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa11",rulelink:"1084651-rule-607-charging",rulenum:"607d(Note1)",question:"Team A's goalkeeper leaves his privileged area to play a puck in the corner of his defensive zone. A Team B player skates into the zone and delivers an avoidable check to the goalkeeper after the goalkeeper passed the puck up the boards. What penalty should the referee assess?",correctanswer:"A minor plus misconduct penalty for charging",incorrectanswers:["No penalty shall be assessed. The goalkeeper is eligible to be checked in this situation","A minor penalty for charging"]},{id:"1usa12",rulelink:"1084982-delaying-the-game",rulenum:"Situation 1",question:"The puck is along the side boards and players from both teams are actively trying to gain possession of the puck but the puck is surrounded by a player's skates. The correct call is:",correctanswer:"No whistle, allow play to continue",incorrectanswers:["Whistle for a frozen puck","Whistle if the puck does not move for four seconds"]},{id:"1usa13",rulelink:"1084652-rule-608-checking-from-behind",rulenum:"608b",question:"What is the minimum penalty that can be assessed to any player who body checks or pushes an opponent from behind causing them to go head first into the boards or goal frame?",correctanswer:"Major plus game misconduct",incorrectanswers:["Minor penalty","Minor plus misconduct."]},{id:"1usa14",rulelink:"1084351-composition-of-teams",rulenum:"Situation 2",question:"Through injuries and penalties, a team becomes unable to place four players on the ice during the game. The game shall be declared a forfeit.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa15",rulelink:"1084571-calling-of-penalties",rulenum:"Situation 8",question:"Team A is one minute into a power play, Team B commits another penalty and the referee has his/her hand up for a delayed call. Before the offending team can get possession and control of the puck, Team A scores",correctanswer:"The penalty currently being served is terminated and the new penalty is assessed and served",incorrectanswers:["The player currently serving a penalty stays in the box, and the delayed penalty is terminated","Both the penalty being served and the delayed penalty are terminated because of the goal"]},{id:"1usa16",rulelink:"1015119-standard-of-play-and-rule-emphasis-body-checking",rulenum:"STANDARD OF PLAY & RULE EMPHASIS - BODY CHECKING",question:"According to the Standard of Play and Rule Emphasis definition of body checking, which of the following is NOT a principle of this enforcement standard?",correctanswer:"The check may be delivered to any area above the shoulders if delivered directly from in front or the side of the opponent",incorrectanswers:["The purpose of a body check is to separate the opponent from the puck","Only the trunk (hips to shoulders) of the body shall be used to deliver a body check"]},{id:"1usa17",rulelink:"1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct",rulenum:"601d(3)",question:"A player bangs the boards with their stick in protest of an official's decision against his/her team. The proper penalty assessment is",correctanswer:"A misconduct or game misconduct and an unsportsmanlike conduct minor.",incorrectanswers:["A minor penalty for unsportsmanlike conduct","A major and a game misconduct"]},{id:"1usa18",rulelink:"1084666-rule-618-handling-puck-with-hands",rulenum:"618b",question:"A hand pass initiated in the defensive zone may be completed in the neutral zone.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"1usa19",rulelink:"1085038-off-sides",rulenum:"Situation 24",question:"Team A, a 12U team, has possession and control of the puck in their defending zone. With a Team B player in Team A's defending zone, Team A attempts a pass that deflects off a Team A player in the neutral zone back into Team A's defending zone. The linesman shall signal a washout for a legal play.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"1usa20",rulelink:"1084985-face-off-locations",rulenum:"Sutuation 1",question:"At a stoppage of play in Team A's defensive zone the following penalties are assessed: #5 from Team A receives a minor penalty for roughing, #12 from Team B receives a minor for slashing and #21 from Team B receives a minor for roughing. Team B will play shorthanded for two minutes. Where is the ensuing face-off?",correctanswer:"Team A's defensive zone",incorrectanswers:["Nearest neutral zone spot","Team B's defensive zone"]},{id:"1usa21",rulelink:"1084675-rule-624-icing-the-puck",rulenum:"624a(Note) & 409a",question:"With a delayed penalty in effect, the non-offending team ices the puck. Where is the ensuing face-off located?",correctanswer:"At a neutral zone face-off spot outside the blue line of the team that iced the puck",incorrectanswers:["At an end zone face-off spot of the penalized team","At an end zone face-off spot of the team that iced the puck"]},{id:"1usa22",rulelink:"1084718-rule-639-tripping-clipping-leg-checking",rulenum:"639b",question:"The penalty options for injuring an opponent due to clipping are:",correctanswer:"Major plus game misconduct",incorrectanswers:["Minor or major plus game misconduct","Match penalty"]},{id:"1usa23",rulelink:"1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct",rulenum:"601e(5)",question:"For the second misconduct assessed to the same player in the same game, a game misconduct penalty shall be assessed to that player in lieu of the second misconduct.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa24",rulelink:"1084688-rule-630-off-sides",rulenum:"630a",question:"A player is offside when they do not have skate contact with any part of the neutral zone or the blue line when the puck crosses the determining edge of the blue line",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa25",rulelink:"1084353-players-in-uniform",rulenum:"Situation 5",question:"A player receives a penalty and is not listed on the scoresheet. The proper action to be taken by the officials is?",correctanswer:"Add the player's name to the scoresheet and assess the penalty as long as the maximum number of players is not already listed on the scoresheet, and assess a bench minor.",incorrectanswers:["Only assess the penalty to the player","Disallow the penalty and tell the player to leave the game"]},{id:"1usa26",rulelink:"1084493-misconduct-penalties",rulenum:"Situation 5",question:"A player has been assessed a second misconduct penalty in the same game. At the time the penalty is assessed, the penalty timekeeper fails to notify the referee that the player has just received his second misconduct in one game, requiring a game misconduct penalty. The situation is brought to the attention of the referee after a few minutes of play following the incident. What action should the referee take?",correctanswer:"After being informed, have the player removed from the game and have the scoresheet reflect the proper assessment.",incorrectanswers:["After being informed at the next stoppage, assess a bench minor to the offending team and assess the game misconduct to the offending player","Since the scorekeeper did not say anything the referee takes no action"]},{id:"1usa27",rulelink:"1015130-zero-tolerance-policy",rulenum:"ZERO TOLERANCE POLICY-Officials",question:"Officials are required to conduct themselves in a businesslike, sportsmanlike, impartial and constructive manner at all times.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa28",rulelink:"1084355-change-of-players",rulenum:"Situation 14",question:"If a player on the penalty bench remains there after the expiration of their penalty (while his/her team is entitled to return to full strength), may his/her team place another skater on the ice as long as the originally penalized player remains on the penalty bench?",correctanswer:"No, the player on the penalty bench must be on the ice and at the bench before they can be substituted",incorrectanswers:["Yes, but his/her team must have possession and control of the puck.","Yes, once the time has expired anyone can join play"]},{id:"1usa29",rulelink:"1084402-rule-304-protective-equipment",rulenum:"304c",question:"It is mandatory that all players (except adults) wear a current (unexpired date) HECC-approved helmet with the chin strap securely fastened.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa30",rulelink:"1089267-goal-scored",rulenum:"GOAL SCORED",question:"The proper signal for a goal scored is pointing at the goal with your non-whistle hand while simultaneously blowing the whistle",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa31",rulelink:"1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations",rulenum:"612b",question:"All face offs during a hockey game will take place at one of the nine (9) designated face-off spots on the ice surface",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa32",rulelink:"1084672-rule-621-high-sticks",rulenum:"621c",question:"Please indicate the proper face-off location: High Sticked puck",correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off",incorrectanswers:["Neutral Zone Face-off spot","Center Ice Face-off spot"]},{id:"1usa33",rulelink:"1015129-codes-of-conduct",rulenum:"On-Ice Official's Code of Conduct",question:"An official should answer all reasonable questions and requests and should admit their mistakes when they make them",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa34",rulelink:"1084405-rule-307-equipment-measurement",rulenum:"307a",question:"A team can request more than one equipment measurement per stoppage of play",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"1usa35",rulelink:"1084356-injured-players",rulenum:"Situation 1",question:"When should you stop play for an injured/hurt player",correctanswer:"Immediately if the injury appears to be serious",incorrectanswers:["Immediately, even if the injury appears to be minor","You must always wait until the injured player's team has possession of the puck"]},{id:"1usa36",rulelink:"1062658-standard-of-play-casebook",rulenum:"Situation 2",question:"According to USA Hockey's Standard of Play initiative, lifting an opponent's stick will always be a penalty",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"1usa37",rulelink:"1084665-rule-617-goals-and-assists",rulenum:"617c(4)",question:"A goal should be disallowed if an attacking player was in the goal crease when the puck entered the goal",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa38",rulelink:"1062658-standard-of-play-casebook",rulenum:"Situation 3",question:"Which of the following is an illigal play according to USA Hockey's Standard of Play Initiative",correctanswer:"Poking the glove of an opponent with the stick, preventing the player from being able to shoot the puck",incorrectanswers:["Using the free arm to maintain their body position while carrying the puck","Both options are illigal"]},{id:"1usa39",rulelink:"1062658-standard-of-play-casebook",rulenum:"Situation 12",question:"According to USA Hockey's Standard of Play Initiative, players are entitled to the ice they occupy as long as they are able to maintain their own foot speed and body position between the puck and opponent",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa40",rulelink:"1084664-rule-616-fouled-from-behind",rulenum:"616a & BM 61",question:"Which is NOT one of the five criteria that has to be met for a penalty shot to be awarded?",correctanswer:"The player is fouled from behind, diagonally from behind, or from the side",incorrectanswers:["The player is deprived of a reasonable scoring opportunity","There is no opponent present between the player and the opposing goalkeeper","The player must be beyond his or her defending blue line (ie neutral and attacking zone)","The player must be in possession and control of the puck"]},{id:"1usa41",rulelink:"1084648-rule-604-body-checking",rulenum:"604b",question:"A boys 12 & Under team is playing a boys 14 & Under team. If both coaches agree:",correctanswer:"Even though the coaches have agreed otherwise, the game must use body contact rules.",incorrectanswers:["The teams may check but only safely.","The teams may use body checking in the game."]},{id:"1usa42",rulelink:"1084477-rule-401-penalties",rulenum:"401b",question:"A player in one game receives a minor penalty for tripping, a double minor for unnecessary roughness, and a minor and misconduct for charging. This player:",correctanswer:"Has five penalties and should be assessed a game misconduct penalty.",incorrectanswers:["Should be told to behave.","Only has four penalties."]},{id:"1usa43",rulelink:"1084654-rule-610-delaying-the-game",rulenum:"610d",question:"A minor penalty for delay of game shall be assessed to a goalkeeper who shoots the puck directly (non deflected) outside of the playing area, except when the puck inadvertently leaves the playing area in a location that is not protected by glass or screen: (example players bench).",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa44",rulelink:"1084688-rule-630-off-sides",rulenum:"630e",question:"A linesman makes an obvious error in stopping play for a puck carried off-sides. The ensuing face-off shall take place at the Center Ice face-off spot",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"1usa45",rulelink:"1084485-rule-408-delayed-penalties",rulenum:"408b",question:"Three (3) players from the same team are on the penalty bench serving non-coincident minor penalties assessed at different times. When the first penalty expires, that player whose penalty expired may return to the ice immediately",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"1usa46",rulelink:"1084489-rule-411-progressive-suspensions",rulenum:"411b(Note)",question:"Officials are required to submit a game report immediately following the game for any major penalty falling in the aggressive infraction category, game misconduct or match penalty that is assessed",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa47",rulelink:"1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct",rulenum:"601e(3)",question:"In addition to a racial/ethnic slur, a match penalty can be assessed for any language that is deemed offensive, hateful ordiscriminatory in nature",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa48",rulelink:"1084674-rule-623-hooking",rulenum:"623b",question:"A major plus a game misconduct penalty shall be assessed to any player who injures an opponent as a result of hooking",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa49",rulelink:"1084718-rule-639-tripping-clipping-leg-checking",rulenum:"639",question:"Tripping, Clipping, Leg Checking and Slew Footing all carry the same penalty options, Minor or Major Penalty OR Major Penalty and Game Misconduct if an injury occurs",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"1usa50",rulelink:"1084676-rule-625-interference",rulenum:"625b",question:"Please indicate the proper face-off location: Goal Crease Violation",correctanswer:"Neutral Zone Face-off ",incorrectanswers:["End Zone Face-off spot","Center Ice Face-off spot."]}]},{id:"2usahall",book:"USA Hockey",level:"2",qa:[{id:"2usa1",rulelink:"1084334-rule-201-composition-of-teams",rulenum:"201b",question:"During the course of a game, a team no longer has a properly registered coach available to them on the bench and adult supervision cannot be found. The game must be forfeited",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa2",rulelink:"1084652-rule-608-checking-from-behind",rulenum:"608c",question:"A player checks an opponent from behind with excessive force while the opponent is in a vulnerable or defenseless position or the action was deemed to be a deliberate attempt to injure an opponent. The proper penalty is a Match Penalty",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa3",rulelink:"1084483-rule-407-goalkeeper-penalties",rulenum:"407a",question:"Please indicate which player serves the penalty: Misconduct assessed to Goalkeeper.",correctanswer:"Player on the ice when the infraction occurred",incorrectanswers:["Player on the bench (non goalkeeper) when the infraction","Offending Player"]},{id:"2usa4",rulelink:"1084338-rule-205-change-of-players",rulenum:"502c",question:"Please indicate the proper face-off location: Premature Goalie Substitution",correctanswer:"Center Ice Face-off spot",incorrectanswers:["Neutral Zone Face-off spot","End Zone Face-off spot"]},{id:"2usa5",rulelink:"1085021-handling-puck-with-hands",rulenum:"Situation 4",question:"The puck is batted with the hand by an attacking player in their attacking zone, \u201cdeflecting\u201d off the opposing goalkeeper. This is an immediate whistle.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa6",rulelink:"1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations",rulenum:"612c",question:"An attacking player in the attacking zone shoots the puck on goal. The puck deflects off the crossbar and goes directly out of play. The face-off takes place at:",correctanswer:"A face off spot in the attacking zone",incorrectanswers:["A neutral zone face off spot","The center ice face off spot"]},{id:"2usa7",rulelink:"1084679-rule-627-kicking-opponent-or-puck",rulenum:"627a",question:"A Match Penalty for Kicking shall be assessed to any player or goalkeeper who uses their skate to 'Push Off' an opponent.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa8",rulelink:"1084590-referee",rulenum:"Situation 6",question:"At the conclusion of the game, the official determines he/she has erred in assessing a checking from behind penalty and assessed a 5-minute major and a misconduct penalty, not a game misconduct penalty. The correct course of action is:",correctanswer:"File a supplemental discipline report",incorrectanswers:["Cross off the misconduct and add the game misconduct at the bottom scoresheet","Let the penalty stand as assessed and call the coach or team mgr"]},{id:"2usa9",rulelink:"1084478-rule-402-minor-penalties",rulenum:"205b & 402b",question:"Please indicate which player serves the penalty: Minor Penalty for Too Many Players on the Ice",correctanswer:"Player on the ice when the infraction occurred",incorrectanswers:["Player on the bench (non goalkeeper) when the infraction","Offending Player"]},{id:"2usa10",rulelink:"1084542-situation-6-charts",rulenum:"Three players on the same team assessed a combination of minor and major penalties. \u201cSig.\u201d = the infraction is being signaled by the Referee when the goal is scored.(Chart 3)",question:"Team A is short-handed by one minor penalty. With play in progress, the Referee signals another minor penalty on Team A. Before play is stopped, Team B scores. The proper action is the minor penalty being served is terminated and the delayed penalty is assessed in the normal manner",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa11",rulelink:"1084663-rule-615-fighting",rulenum:"615c",question:"A game misconduct penalty shall be assessed to any player whose helmet/facemask was not worn properly and comes off their head during an altercation",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa12",rulelink:"1084675-rule-624-icing-the-puck",rulenum:"624b(1)",question:"A shorthanded team shall not be allowed to legally ice the puck at the 16 & Under level or below",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa13",rulelink:"1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations",rulenum:"612d",question:"A stoppage of play in an end zone is followed by a gathering of players. The ensuing face off shall take place in the neutral zone if any of the attacking players enter the zone further than the outer edge of the face off circles",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa14",rulelink:"1084973-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct",rulenum:"Situation 7 & 601b(1)",question:"Which of the following would NOT result in a misconduct penalty?",correctanswer:"Profane language by the coach",incorrectanswers:["Mouthpiece violation","Player throws equipment out of the rink"]},{id:"2usa15",rulelink:"1084482-rule-406-penalty-shot",rulenum:"406c",question:"Please indicate the proper face-off location: Unsuccessful Penalty shot attempt",correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off spot",incorrectanswers:["Neutral Zone Face-off spot","Center Ice Face-off spot"]},{id:"2usa16",rulelink:"1084334-rule-201-composition-of-teams",rulenum:"201a",question:"A team may dress (3) Goalkeepers and (17) skaters",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa17",rulelink:"1084578-rule-501-appointment-of-officials",rulenum:"501a",question:"The three-official system (one Referee/two Linesman) and the two-official system (two Referee\u2019s) are the only approved systems for USA Hockey sanctioned games. Districts or Affiliates are authorized to use the four-official system (two Referee\u2019s and two Linesman) for gamesinvolving teams in the Youth and Girls\u2019 16 & under age classifications and older (including High School and Adults).",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa18",rulelink:"1084455-protective-equipment",rulenum:"Situation 1",question:"Keeping safety as the primary consideration, the referee should stop play whenever the goalkeeper loses a glove and is in a vulnerable position, UNLESS there is an imminent scoring opportunity in which play should be allowed to continue until the imminent scoring opportunity has passed",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa19",rulelink:"1084406-rule-308-electronic-devices",rulenum:"308b",question:"An electronic device may be used to challenge an official's call if the team uses its time-out to do so",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa20",rulelink:"1084353-players-in-uniform",rulenum:"Situation 4",question:"Players that are ineligible for the game should be crossed off the scoresheet at the conclusion of the game",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa21",rulelink:"1084681-rule-628-kneeing",rulenum:"628",question:"The penalty options for Kneeing an opponent are",correctanswer:"Minor or Major penalty. Major plus game misconduct if injury occurs",incorrectanswers:["Minor plus misconduct","Match Penalty"]},{id:"2usa22",rulelink:"1084485-rule-408-delayed-penalties",rulenum:"408c",question:"Two players from Team A are assessed non-coincidental penalties at the same time. Player 34 is assessed a minor and player 16 a major. Which penalty is recorded first?",correctanswer:"The minor penalty to Player 34.",incorrectanswers:["The major penalty to Player 16.","Captain\u2019s choice as to which penalty."]},{id:"2usa23",rulelink:"1084654-rule-610-delaying-the-game",rulenum:"610c",question:"The puck is deliberately shot or batted out of play. This will result in:",correctanswer:"A minor penalty to the offending player or goalkeeper.",incorrectanswers:["A face-off at the nearest face-off location.","A face-off at the nearest face-off location with no change for the offending team."]},{id:"2usa24",rulelink:"1084491-minor-penalties",rulenum:"Situation 18",question:"Player A receives a minor penalty. Prior to the ensuing face-off, a Team B player receives a minor penalty. The two penalties are considered coincidental even though they were not committed at the same time",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa25",rulelink:"1084666-rule-618-handling-puck-with-hands",rulenum:"618a",question:"A player closes his hand on the puck and does not drop it immediately to the ice. The officials should:",correctanswer:"Stop play and conduct a last play face-off.",incorrectanswers:["Assess the player a minor penalty for delay of game.","Do nothing as long as the player does not take more than one stride."]},{id:"2usa26",rulelink:"1084493-misconduct-penalties",rulenum:"Situation 4",question:"During a Youth game, a player is assessed a non-coincident major plus game misconduct penalty and is removed from the game. Who must serve the major penalty and when must he enter the penalty bench",correctanswer:"Any non-penalized player (non goalkeeper) and must enter penalty bench immediately",incorrectanswers:["Offending Player who must enter penalty bench immediately","Player on the ice when the infraction occurred and must enter penalty bench prior to expiration of the major penalty"]},{id:"2usa27",rulelink:"1084651-rule-607-charging",rulenum:"607d(Note1)",question:"Any deliberate body contact or check that is delivered to the goalkeeper shall be penalized as charging",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa28",rulelink:"1015130-zero-tolerance-policy",rulenum:"ZERO TOLERANCE POLICY - Parents/Spectators",question:"An official is NOT allowed to stop a game if parents/spectators display inappropriate and disruptive behavior that interferes with other spectators of the game. Officials are only responsible for what happens on the ice.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa29",rulelink:"1084688-rule-630-off-sides",rulenum:"630c",question:"Please indicate the proper face-off location: Intentional offside",correctanswer:"End Zone Face-off spot",incorrectanswers:["Neutral Zone Face-off spot","Center Ice Face-off spot"]},{id:"2usa30",rulelink:"1084580-rule-503-linesman",rulenum:"503(c, d & e)",question:"Which can a linesman NOT stop play for?",correctanswer:"A coach taunting an opponent.",incorrectanswers:["A goal unobserved by the referee.","Articles thrown on the ice from the players bench."]},{id:"2usa31",rulelink:"1085038-off-sides",rulenum:"630d Sit. 34 & 624a",question:"A player in a game where the delayed off-sides rule applies shoots the puck from his defending half of the neutral zone across his opponent\u2019s goal line. A teammate is completely over his attacking blue line before the puck crosses that blue line and is therefore off-side (non-intentional situation). The play is stopped and the face-off is held at the:",correctanswer:"Nearest end zone face-off spot of the team icing the puck.",incorrectanswers:["Nearest neutral zone face off-spot","Linesman\u2019s choice of face-off spots."]},{id:"2usa32",rulelink:"1084338-rule-205-change-of-players",rulenum:"205d",question:"A player serving a penalty on the penalty bench, whose penalty has expired must proceed by way of the ice to the player\u2019s bench. His substitute may start onto the ice at the expiration of the penalty.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa33",rulelink:"1084338-rule-205-change-of-players",rulenum:"205a",question:"While play is in progress a team is changing players. A player entering the game is accidentally struck by the puck while the player he is changing for is still on the ice. A too many players on the ice minor penalty should be assessed.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa34",rulelink:"1084398-rule-301-stickss",rulenum:"301e",question:"A player who is carrying a replacement stick to the goalkeeper and is accidentally struck by the puck while in possession of two sticks should be assessed a minor penalty.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa35",rulelink:"1084405-rule-307-equipment-measurement",rulenum:"307b",question:"A referee may not legally measure a stick without a request from the opposing team.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa36",rulelink:"1084489-rule-411-progressive-suspensions",rulenum:"411a",question:"Under Rule 411 (progressive suspensions), the major penalties must be for the same infraction to count toward the players\u2019 three-game, five-game or indefinite suspension.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa37",rulelink:"1084402-rule-304-protective-equipment",rulenum:"304f",question:"A player may wear a clear (non-colored) mouthguard as long as the official is notified prior to the start of the game.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa38",rulelink:"1084335-rule-202-captain-of-team",rulenum:"202a",question:"The referee notices during warm-ups that all players on one team, including the goalkeepers, have \u201cC\u201ds on their uniforms. This is permitted as long as the team designates one captain and not more than two alternates on the scoresheet prior to the start of the game.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa39",rulelink:"1084584-rule-507-penalty-timekeeper",rulenum:"507c",question:"To make more room for the players and coaches on the players\u2019 bench, it is permissable for the backup goaltender to occupy the penalty bench",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa40",rulelink:"1084718-rule-639-tripping-clipping-leg-checking",rulenum:"639a(2)",question:"A player dives (leaves his feet) and sweeps the puck away from his opponent. The follow through of the sweeping action causes the opponent to trip and fall to the ice. Because the defending player made contact and swept the puck away before his opponent tripped, a penalty for tripping should NOT be called.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa41",rulelink:"1084477-rule-401-penalties",rulenum:"401b & 411b",question:"Any team that receives three or more major penalties, or fifteen or more penalties, in the same game shall have its head coach suspended for the team\u2019s next game. However, he is not assessed a game misconduct penalty.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa42",rulelink:"1084645-rule-601-abuse-of-officials-and-other-misconduct",rulenum:"601e(2)",question:"Depending upon how objectionable it is, an obscene gesture may result in a misconduct or game misconduct penalty.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa43",rulelink:"1084657-rule-612-face-off-locations",rulenum:"612f",question:"The puck is shot by the attacking team in the neutral zone. It strikes an official and goes directly into the goal. There is no goal and the resulting face-off should take place at the nearest face-off spot to where the puck was shot.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa44",rulelink:"1084660-rule-613-face-off-procedures",rulenum:"613e",question:"A minor penalty for interference shall be assessed to any player facing-off who makes any physical contact with his opponent\u2019s body by means of his own body or by his stick except in the course of playing the puck after the face-off has been completed.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa45",rulelink:"1085023-head-butting",rulenum:"619b Sit. 1 & 305b",question:"A player with taped hands injures an opponent during an altercation. During the same altercation he head-butts the same opponent. Because the same opponent was fouled only one match penalty should be assessed.",correctanswer:"False",incorrectanswers:["True"]},{id:"2usa46",rulelink:"1085025-high-sticks",rulenum:"621b Sit. 3",question:'A major penalty and a game misconduct penalty for high sticking should be assessed to a player who checked and who is body checked, as he is falling to the ice, cuts an opponent on the head with his "high" stick?',correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa47",rulelink:"1084688-rule-630-off-sides",rulenum:"630d(5)",question:"An attacking player in a game where the delayed off-sides rule applies shoots the puck from the neutral zone and directly on goal with a teammate off-sides. The goalie makes the save and starts to pass the puck to his teammate. The linesman should:",correctanswer:"Stop play immediately for an off-side infraction.",incorrectanswers:["Allow play to continue if attacking players are attempting to tag-up","Either option depending upon the certainty of the goalkeeper's save."]},{id:"2usa48",rulelink:"1084660-rule-613-face-off-procedures",rulenum:"613d",question:"A second face-off violation shall result in a delay of game penalty if it occurs:",correctanswer:"By the same team during the same face-off.",incorrectanswers:["By the same team anytime during the game.","By the same player anytime during the game."]},{id:"2usa49",rulelink:"1084662-rule-614-falling-on-puck",rulenum:"614c",question:"A minor penalty for delay of game shall be assessed to any goalkeeper who falls on or gathers the puck into his body and causes a stoppage of play when the puck is outside the boundaries of the goalkeeper's privileged area.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]},{id:"2usa50",rulelink:"1018530-appendix-iv-official-rink-diagrams",rulenum:"Rink Diagram",question:"The two-inch thick red line outlining the goal crease is considered to be part of the goal crease.",correctanswer:"True",incorrectanswers:["False"]}]}],W=function(e,t){var a=B.filter((function(t){return t.book===e}));return"all"!==t&&(a=a.filter((function(e){return e.level===t}))),a},_=function(e){Object(u.a)(a,e);var t=Object(h.a)(a);function a(e){var n;return Object(i.a)(this,a),(n=t.call(this,e)).filterClick=n.filterClick.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.handleLogInClick=n.handleLogInClick.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.handleChange=n.handleChange.bind(Object(c.a)(n)),n.state={isFiltered:!1,user:"",isShowLogIn:!0,newdata:W("USA Hockey","1")},n}return Object(l.a)(a,[{key:"handleChange",value:function(e){this.setState({user:e.target.value})}},{key:"handleLogInClick",value:function(e){e.preventDefault(),console.log(this.state.user),this.setState({isShowLogIn:!1})}},{key:"filterClick",value:function(e,t){console.log("testfilter",e),console.log("levelfilter",t),this.setState({isFiltered:!0,newdata:W(e,t)})}},{key:"render",value:function(){var e=this.state.newdata;return r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(x,{fclick:this.filterClick}),this.state.isShowLogIn?r.a.createElement(L,{show:this.state.isShowLogIn,showclick:this.handleLogInClick,user:this.handleChange}):r.a.createElement(S,{datafilter:e}))}}]),a}(r.a.Component);Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));a(78),a(79);o.a.render(r.a.createElement("div",null,r.a.createElement(_,null)),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then((function(e){e.unregister()})).catch((function(e){console.error(e.message)}))}},[[51,1,2]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.a73b2833.chunk.js.map